<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, VTLActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">VTL</string>
    <string name="vtllogo">VITRUAL TRIP LINES</string>
    <string name="hello1">Virtual Trip Lines</string>
    <string name="succreg">Hello User, Successfully Registered</string>
    <string name="terminate">Sorry, Process Terminated</string>
    <string name="failreg">Registration Failure</string>
    <string name="proceed">                                    Proceed</string>
    <string name="hello11">Virtual Trip Lines     				||      		    	Virtual Trip Lines      		||</string>
    <string name="hello2">Enhancing Privacy and Accuracy in Probe Vehicle-Based Traffic Monitoring via Virtual Trip Lines</string>
	<string name="hello3">Traffic monitoring using probe vehicles with GPS receivers promises significant improvements in cost, coverage, and
accuracy over dedicated infrastructure systems. Current approaches, however, raise privacy concerns because they require
participants to reveal their positions to an external traffic monitoring server. To address this challenge, we describe a system based on
virtual trip lines and an associated cloaking technique, followed by another system design in which we relax the privacy requirements to
maximize the accuracy of real-time traffic estimation. We introduce virtual trip lines which are geographic markers that indicate where
vehicles should provide speed updates. These markers are placed to avoid specific privacy sensitive locations. They also allow
aggregating and cloaking several location updates based on trip line identifiers, without knowing the actual geographic locations of
these trip lines. Thus, they facilitate the design of a distributed architecture, in which no single entity has a complete knowledge of
probe identities and fine-grained location information. 
</string>   
<string name="registration">User Registration</string>
<string name="login">User Login</string>
<string name="server_url0">http://10.0.0.11:9999/VTL/</string>
<string name="server_url">http://</string>
<string name="server_url1">:9999/VTL/</string>
<string name="server_url2">>http://115.241.70.76:9999/VTL/</string>
<string name="proxy_ip">10.0.0.11</string>
<string name="proxy_port">8090</string>   
<string name="username">UserName</string>
<string name="userid">User Id.</string>
<string name="password">Password</string>
<string name="gender">Gender</string>
<string name="male">Male</string>
<string name="female">Female</string> 
<string name="mobileno">Mobile No</string>
<string name="emailid">E Mail Id</string>
<string name="submit">Submit</string>

<string name="requestid">"Request Id.</string>
<string name="updatevtl">Launch</string> 
<string name="updatevtl1">Speed_Direction</string>
<string name="welcometo">Welcome to</string>
<string name="vtl">Virtual Trip Lines</string>
</resources>
